[Speaker 01] Can I ask a question? Of course you can.
[Speaker 02] Can
[Speaker 01] you get me out of this place?
[Speaker 02] I'm afraid I'm of no use to you there. Why
[Speaker 01] couldn't they put me in a proper prison?
[Speaker 02] A better facility wasn't available. Put me in a madhouse?
[Speaker 01] It's secure training centre. Training?
[Speaker 02] What are they training us
[Speaker 01] for? The other boys are screaming all the time. I had been
[Speaker 02] explained to And the rock backwards and forwards and the shower at current
[Speaker 01] age is free. Young institutions have got 15
[Speaker 02] up. One kid goes nuts every time you see Steve McDonald.
[Speaker 01] It's mad in here, you don't understand. This was the best place for you to Ryan gets to
[Speaker 02] stay at home until his trial. Ryan isn't accused of
[Speaker 01] such a serious crime. Accused?
[Speaker 02] It's all accused. If I did it,
[Speaker 01] if I hurt her, then I get it, but I didn't,
[Speaker 02] so... I it, Jamie, and this wasn't my decision. This was the best place for you to
[Speaker 01] be. Nothing has been decided yet. Do know where it's going to be? London or somewhere local? You
[Speaker 02] need to sit down, Jamie.
[Speaker 01] If you don't sit down... Does that mean you don't know
[Speaker 02] what you just want to tell me? Nothing's been decided yet.
[Speaker 01] You need to sit down. I don't want to sit down. If you don't
[Speaker 02] sit down, I have to stop this discussion. Maybe I want you to. Do
[Speaker 01] you? It'd piss you off, that, wouldn't it?
[Speaker 02] You'd have to go home and then come back again.
[Speaker 01] Jamie, if you do not sit... Look how fucking what I sit down!
[Speaker 02] You do not tell me when to sit down!
[Speaker 01] You do not control what I
[Speaker 02] fucking... Look at me now!
[Speaker 01] You do not
[Speaker 02] control what I do in my life! Get
[Speaker 01] that in that fucking little head of yours!
[Speaker 02] Fucking hell!